Hello everyone, this is Kanami, my name is Kanami!
Yes, that's right.
Today.
I'm going to visit the super time-honored hall tour 2023 that I'm going to make with the advertising department members.
10 gourmet souvenirs and sightseeing spots in Japan!
I'd like to recommend 10 gourmet souvenirs and sightseeing spots in Japan!
This is the last one!
The 10th stop, Tokyo!
Tokyo, Tokyo
On Saturday, September 9th
Saturday, September 9th
This will be the last day of the hall tour.
It all happened so fast.
I think Tokyo had fewer recommendations than other prefectures...
I'd like to share your recommendations with you as soon as possible!
Let's start with gourmet food!
Let's start with food!
In terms of recommendations near the venue...
This is one of the most popular ones.
Niboshi Shoyu Ramen at Menwaso!
Nice, a little refreshing ramen, isn't it?
Lightly seasoned!
Seafood ramen with a thick broth!
I love it!
I love seafood ramen!
It looks like there's a place in front of the venue.
I'd love to go there before the concert!
There are other ramen shops that look pretty good too, so please check them out!
And next, I must go to a restaurant called Tambo, which serves Japanese set menus.
It seems to be a Japanese-style set menu restaurant, and it was recommended to me by a member of the Shoujo Shogakusei Advertising Department.
I think this is very good information!
This restaurant was established in 1996 and specializes in delicious rice.
They serve freshly cooked rice of various varieties imported from rice-producing regions all over Japan!
It seems that the rice is purchased on a periodic basis, which is great, because it makes me happy to be able to eat delicious rice.
The store opens at 8:00 in the morning.The restaurant is open from 8:00 in the morning.
Everyone should try it for breakfast!
And the hamburger steak curry at Bistro Chiracute!
Nice hamburger steak!
It seems that hamburger steak curry with plenty of gravy is very popular!
Shibakari Straw, one of the best Indian curry made by Japanese
You can eat Indian curry in Japan!
No wonder it's so popular among Indian food connoisseurs!
There are only a handful of places that can make Indian food connoisseurs and curry connoisseurs
Only a handful of restaurants can satisfy the palates of Indian food connoisseurs and curry connoisseurs.
I didn't know it was that good!
Also, there's Wasshin, a restaurant specializing in aged sushi!
Wow, that's really good sushi!
The ultimate sushi!
Wow!
It overturns the conventional wisdom
It overturns conventional wisdom. For anniversaries and celebrations.
I love it! It looks so delicious!
This is the best!
I want to eat sushi like this.
It's like a work of art!
Shinjuku Yakiniku Beef tongue with lemon!
Julia told me about this place, and I've always wanted to try it. They have really thick beef tongue.
Hishida's ginger yaki is one of the three best in Japan.
I'd like to try that. And there are many stylish cafes in Sangen-jaya.
Nice. So there are many cafes in Sangen-jaya.
There's a place called Coffee & Toast.
I wondered what it was.
I wondered what it was, but it had a strong impact on me.
They have a lot of toast on the menu.
There's a lot of buzz.
I've never seen anything like it.
I really want you to see this.
I don't know if I can eat it all by myself.The toast is so big that I'm not sure if I can eat it all by myself!
It looks like it's located near the shaved ice place of the Japanese Kitchen Viewing, so if you're looking for a hot day, go there!
If you want to eat ice, please go there! Next is a souvenir!
Next is a souvenir shop, 12 Minutes Bakery, which is a combination of a florist and a bakery.
I love it when people are happy just by being in style, and I love it when people are happy.
And there's a sweet called "berry ruby cut".
It's a cute little jewelry shaped pastry, but it's a great souvenir to take home.
And Monteblanco at L'atelier Mort statue!
It's so good, it floats!
I want to try it! People say it's the best Mont Blanc they've ever tasted!
I'd like to try it.
Cocoa-flavored meringue, marron cream, and fresh cream on top of that.
I heard this type of Mont Blanc is common in Italy.
So this Mont Blanc is Italian style.
I want to try it even more. It's so stylish!
And there's also a baked sweet potato shop called Shinomoto Mihara Chaya.
Julia and Akichan want to go there for sure!
It looks so delicious!
They have sweet potato sweets and baked potatoes.
And they have ice cream too!
They even have sweet potato cakes!
And then...
Chiffon cake from Ma Service!
I love it so much that I often go there to eat it or buy it to take home.
They also have a variety of other flavors, including matcha (powdered green tea), which is also delicious!
And the New York Caramel Sandwich, which is a cookie with caramel inside.
It's so popular that even in Tokyo, people still stand in line at certain times of the day.
People in my old city love it and always ask me to buy them this New York caramel sandwich when I go back home.
They always ask me to buy them a large quantity when I go home.
I think everyone likes it.
I think there are a lot of people who like it!
That's all I have to say about souvenirs!
Next, let's take a look at the tourist attractions!
Here you go.
Tokyo Tower, Sky Tree... the classic.
And the view from the Carrot Tower, which is also quite beautiful.The view from the Carrot Tower was also quite beautiful. Todoroki Canyon
There is a lot of greenery here, too. It looks like a great place to take pictures.
And then there's the power spot at the Mage Shrine.
It's one of the most famous power spots in Tokyo, and I wonder how many times I've been there.
I've been there several times since I joined Stardust, and I've actually used the well as a standby tower.
This power spot, Kiyomasa's well.
And also Shibuya Sky... it's pretty high up and you can see the city of Shibuya.
And you can make your own snow globe at the snow globe museum, so you can make your own original snow globe.
So that's my introduction to Tokyo.
I'm sure there are many delicious foods in Tokyo, so I hope you all enjoy sightseeing in Tokyo.
And this time, I asked Julia what her favorite restaurant in Tokyo is, and here it is!
Here it is!
Okay, today I'm going to ask Julia...
I'd like to ask Julia what she recommends for food, souvenirs, or tourist attractions in Tokyo.
I'd like to ask Julia what she recommends as a gourmet meal, souvenir or tourist attraction in Tokyo. Do you have any?
Yes, I do.
Gillian recommends Espresso D Works.
It's a café by day and a restaurant by night.
Oh, what kind of restaurant?
Some kind of restaurant?
Pasta, salmon, all kinds of individual dishes.
Wow, that sounds delicious!
They have delicious cheesecakes with salt. Cheesecakes with salt.
I love that kind of thing! The pancakes are really good too!
Looks so delicious! I recommend this place. I go there often.
I was there yesterday too.
Thank you very much for the good information.
I heard there's one in Emmis, too.
Yes, I'll go there too.
Bye bye.
Yes, and I hope you'll try Jillia's recommendation, too.
Okay, everyone, this is the last time I'm going to introduce you to a total of 10 places for food and souvenirs.
I hope you all enjoyed this last article, in which I introduced a total of 10 tourist attractions with gourmet food and souvenirs.
I hope you all enjoyed it. When I go on a private trip, I will enjoy myself by referring to your recommendations.
I hope you all enjoyed yourselves and I'll be sure to use your recommendations as a guide when I go on my own private tours.
I hope you all have a great time in Tokyo and I look forward to seeing you all at the tour finale.Have fun in Tokyo, and we look forward to seeing you at the tour finale.
See you next week!